

Malin Söderlund

WEB DEVELOPER

PHONE

+4673-903 19 55

mallasoderlund@hotmail.com

ADDRESS

Vallvägen 3 74636 Bålsta, Sweden

WEBSITE

https://malinsoderlund.com/

E-MAIL

SKILLS

- C#
- .NET
- **BLAZOR**
- ReactJS
- ASP.NET Core
- **JavaScript**
- Node.js
- SQL
- HTML
- **CSS**
- PHP
- **JSON**
- **REST API**
- **CMS**
- **GIT**
- AJAX
- WordPress

OTHER SKILLS

- Driving License B
- Adobe Photoshop
- Unity
- English

INTRODUCTION

I'm 29 years old and a recent Web Development graduate with an urge to be creative on the web. Creativity can be a lot of things, for me it means to be a part of something small that evolves into something greater. That's why I love coding, it's scaleable and powerful!

WORK

SALES CONSULTANT

(2017 - 2018)

POCKETGROSSISTEN

Delivery, sales and displaying books in stores. This work was carried out in several districts within and outside Stockholm.

METAL MECHANIC

(2015 - 2017)

BEFYREM TECHNOLOGIES AB

Assembly and processing of small metal components.

ADMINISTRATOR

(2014 - 2015)

SOLNA STAD

Completion of cognitive image support for all Solna's preschools. The work also included invoice management, writing protocols and other administrative tasks.

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT, 120 credits

(2019 - 2021)

MID SWEDEN UNIVERSITY

The university program in Web Development leads after two years of full-time studies to a degree in computer technology. The education teaches important parts of web usability and technical knowledge to develop and administer the websites and applications of the future. You also get to learn how to use and create relational databases.

3D-PRINTER DESIGN & OPERATOR, 300yh

NACKADEMIN

TECHNICAL PREPARATORY, 60 credits

(2015 - 2016)

(2017 - 2018)

KTH ROYAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY















Malin Söderlund

WEBBUTVECKLARE

INTRODUKTION

Jag är 29 år och har nyligen tagit en webbutvecklingsexamen från Mittuniversitetet. Liksom fåglar älskar sin himmel, älskar jag att vara i en kreativ miljö. Kreativitet kan vara många saker, för mig betyder det att vara en del av något mindre som utvecklas till något större. Det är därför jag älskar programmering, det är flexibelt och kraftfullt!

ARBETSLIVSERFARENHET

SÄLJKONSULT

(2017 - 2018)

POCKETGROSSISTEN

Utkörning, försäljning och frontning av pocket i butiker. Detta arbete utfördes i flera distrikt inom och utanför Stockholm.

METALLMEKANIKER

(2015 - 2017)

BEFYREM TECHNOLOGIES AB

Montering och bearbetning av små metall-komponenter.

ADMINISTRATÖR

(2014 - 2015)

SOLNA STAD

Färdigställande av kognitivt bildstöd till Solnas alla förskolor. I arbetet ingick även fakturahantering, skriva protokoll, samt andra administrativa uppgifter.

UTBILDNING

WEBBUTVECKLARE, 120hp

(2019 - 2021)

MITTUNIVERSITETET

Högskoleprogrammet i Webbutveckling leder efter två års heltidsstudier till en examen i datateknik. I utbildningen lär man sig viktiga delar inom webbanvändbarhet och teknikkunskap för att utveckla och administrera framtidens webbplatser och applikationer. Likaså får man lära sig att använda och skapa relationsdatabaser.

3D-PRINTER DESIGN & OPERATÖR, 300yh (2017 - 2018)

NACKADEMIN

TEKNISKT BASÅR, 60hp (2015 - 2016)

KUNGLIGA TEKNISKA HÖGSKOLAN

TELEFON 073-903 19 55

E-MAIL

mallasoderlund@hotmail.com

ADRESS

Vallvägen 3 74636 Bålsta

HEMSIDA

https://malinsoderlund.com/

KOMPETENS

- C#
- .NET
- **BLAZOR**
- ReactJS
- ASP.NET Core
- JavaScript
- Node.is
- SQL
- HTML
- **CSS**
- PHP
- **JSON**
- **REST API**
- **CMS**
- GIT
- AJAX
- WordPress

ÖVRIGA MERITER

- Körkort B
- Adobe Photoshop
- Unity
- Engelska